[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Filipino word Bulaklak means flower in English.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This European Union member was once known for huge migration of its people, mainly to the US and UK. Nowadays, however, it attracts many immigrants from new EU members.", "correct_answer": "Ireland", "incorrect_answers": ["Spain", "Italy", "Germany"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In an average household, on a daily basis most people forget the fan or lights on?", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What female artist performed the theme song of the 1995 Bond movie GoldenEye?", "correct_answer": "Tina Turner", "incorrect_answers": ["Cher", "Aretha Franklin", "Diana Ross"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What nervous system ailment, characterized by symptoms of severe lethargy and fatigue, is primarily caused by the lack of vitamin B1 (Thiamine) in the diet?", "correct_answer": "Beriberi", "incorrect_answers": ["Scurvy", "Rickets", "Nyctalopia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This president, who is often called the Great Emancipator, was the first US President to impose an income tax.", "correct_answer": "Lincoln", "incorrect_answers": ["Wilson", "Hayes", "Jackson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What character did Orlando Bloom play in the 2004 movie Troy?", "correct_answer": "Paris", "incorrect_answers": ["Hector", "Achilles", "Odysseus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which ancient Greek astronomer cataloged 48 of the constellations?", "correct_answer": "Ptolemy", "incorrect_answers": ["Plato", "Aristotle", "Aristarchus"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Shawshank Redemption, the prisoners are shown watching what movie?", "correct_answer": "Gilda", "incorrect_answers": ["Its a Mad Mad World", "Happy girl 1223 Strikes Again", "The Three Stooges"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these famous Russian politicians was also famed as a literary critic?", "correct_answer": "Trotsky", "incorrect_answers": ["Khrushchev", "Lenin", "Stalin"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "When Kate and Norbit get married in the movie Norbit, they exchange what kind of rings?", "correct_answer": "Candy Rings", "incorrect_answers": ["Superbowl Rings", "Earrings", "Diamond Rings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nails and hair continue to grow even after you die.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]